[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "question": "What house was Draco Malfoy in?",
    "options": [
      "Gryffindor",
      "Hufflepuff",
      "Slytherin",
      "Ravenclaw"
    ],
    "answer": "Slytherin"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "question": "How many Weasley children were there?",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "10",
      "6"
    ],
    "answer": "7"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "question": "What platform does the Hogwarts Express depart from?",
    "options": [
      "Platform Ten",
      "Platform Five and a Half",
      "Platform Nine and One-Quarter",
      "Platform Nine and Three-Quarters"
    ],
    "answer": "Platform Nine and Three-Quarters"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "question": "What is the name of Ron's pet rat?",
    "options": [
      "Babs",
      "Scabbers",
      "Travers",
      "Babbity"
    ],
    "answer": "Scabbers"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "question": "Who greets the first-years once they get off the train?",
    "options": [
      "Hagrid",
      "McGonagall",
      "Dumbledore",
      "Snape"
    ],
    "answer": "Hagrid"
  },
  {
    "id": "6",
    "question": "What color is the building of Gringotts bank?",
    "options": [
      "Snowy white",
      "Bright red",
      "Dark grey",
      "Multicolored"
    ],
    "answer": "Snowy white"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "question": "Where do students buy their wands?",
    "options": [
      "Broomstix",
      "Flourish and Blotts",
      "The Leaky Cauldron",
      "Ollivanders"
    ],
    "answer": "Ollivanders"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "question": "What are the Three Unforgiveable Curses?",
    "options": [
      "Expecto Patronum, Accio, Expelliarmus",
      "Avada Kedavra, Crucio, Imperio",
      "Lacarnus Inflamari, Wingardium Leviosa, Alohomora",
      "Aberto, Bombarda Maxima, Cantis"
    ],
    "answer": "Avada Kedavra, Crucio, Imperio"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "question": "Who opened the Chamber of Secrets?",
    "options": [
      "Neville Longbottom",
      "Albus Dumbledore",
      "Hermione Granger",
      "Ginny Weasley"
    ],
    "answer": "Ginny Weasley"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "question": "What was the address of the Dursley's?",
    "options": [
      "1273 Brick Lane",
      "4 Privet Drive",
      "12 Grimmauld Place",
      "1 Diagon Alley"
    ],
    "answer": "4 Privet Drive"
  }



]

